Guide to the Duke University Union Records, 1954-ongoing UA.09.13.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Records1954-ongoing, 54 boxes
  - Special Events: General, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Purgatory, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Comedy Spot, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, October 9, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Homecoming, Comedy Spot, Mano Joyner, October 24, 1992 (Box 38)
  - University Union Board: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Computers, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Restructuring/Constitutions, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - SALAPS [Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program], 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee: Proposals, Spring 1993 (Box 38)
  - Union Board: Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee: Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Budgets, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Finance: Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Budgets, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Fall Retreat, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Oktoberfest, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Art Events: Permanent File, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Pictures of Peace, October 26-November 28, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Cable 13: Permanent File, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Permanent File, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Max Halperen, August 26-September 25, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Vickie Mitchell, September 26-October 26, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: David Stratton, October 15-November 22, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Ellen Reinhold, January 24-February 22, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Kip Frace and J.P. Errico, February 24-March 29, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Livia Stein, March 28-April 23, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Charlie Nestor, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - On Stage: Cosponsorships, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Interaction: Permanent File, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: General, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: Donations, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: Once On This Island, September 8-9, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: General, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Purgatory, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Comedy Spot, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Finance, Summer, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Media Festival Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: They Might By Giants, September 22, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: Cracker, October 27, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Interaction: Grad Student for a Day, November, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: Buddy, November 1-2, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: Dillon Fence, November 6, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: Toad the Wet Sprocket, November 11, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: 10,000 Maniacs, November 15, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Paul Gerni, November 17, 1992 (Box 38)
  - On Stage: Campaign Murder, November 23, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: Roger Manning, November 23, 1992 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, December 7, 1992 (Box 38)
  - On Stage: Arsenio Hall Writers, January 23, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: The Goats, January 24, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Major Speakers: Tsongas/Rudman, January 24, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: Lend Me A Tenor, January 24-25, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Interaction: The Meeting, February 15, 1993 (Box 38)
  - On Stage: Martha Graham Ensemble, February 28, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: Tru, March 2-3, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Broadway at Duke: Flying Karamazov Brothers, March 10-11, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Interaction: Mark Mathabane, March 11, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Major Attractions: Soul Asylum, March 30, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Springfest, April 16, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Special Events: Springfest Concert, April 16, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Dorothy Arnold, April 23-May 28, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Interaction: Life 101, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Nerys Levy, May 26-July 7, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Galleries: Robert You, July 7-August 23, 1993 (Box 38)
  - University Union Board: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - On Stage: Langston and Martin (Danny Glover), January 23, 1993 (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Facilities: Minutes, 1991-1993 (Box 38)
  - Facilities: Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Finance: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Letters from the President, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Visual Arts: Surveys, etc., 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Visual Arts: Pictures of Peace, October, 1992 (Box 38)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Programming: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Bryan Center Privatization, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  - Officers, 1992-1994 (Box 38)
  - Executive Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Program Council: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Facilities/Finance: Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Memos to/from VP Dickerson, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - ReUnion, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Craft Center, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Bryan Center, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Financial Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Interaction, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Duke Media, Summer 1993 (Box 42)
  - Summer Programming, 1993 (Box 42)
  - Agendas/Minutes, 1992-1994 (Box 42)
  - Life 101, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - General Information, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - UUB and Union Events, 1992-1993 (Box 42)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes/Agendas, 1993-2001 (Box 39)
  - Executive Committee: General Expenses, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Interview Process/Review, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Proposals to Executive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Finance: Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Student-Run Organizations, 1993-1995 (Box 39)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1994 (Box 39)
  - Club Listings, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Student-Run Organizations, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Marketing Information, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Yearlook: Newsletters, circa 1994 (Box 39)
  - Yearlook: Budgets, circa 1994 (Box 39)
  - Denials, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Songs That Were More Trouble Than They Were Worth, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - UUB/Executive Board, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Blank Office Space Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Music Rights, 1991-1993 (Box 39)
  - Office Space Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Union Orientation Program, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Executive Committee: Proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Budgets, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: VHS Transfers, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Deep Dish TV Network, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Visiting Journalists Program, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Internships, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchases, Van and Studio, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Paper Tiger TV, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: Policies, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Program Enrichment Fund: Applications, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Program Enrichment Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Constitution and ASDU By-Laws, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Executive Committee: Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Retreats, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Galleries: Floor Plans, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Galleries: Off-Campus Galleries/Spaces, circa 1994 (Box 39)
  - Galleries: Contracts, 1993 (Box 39)
  - Galleries: Comments, circa 1994 (Box 39)
  - Galleries: Miscellaneous Finance, 1984-1994 (Box 39)
  - Arts Facilities Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 39)
  - Special Events, 1992-1994 (Box 39)
  - Major Attractions, 1988-1994 (Box 39)
  - Major Attractions, January, 1994 (Box 39)
  - Theater Facilities Users Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 39)
  - Cable 13: General, 1987-1993 (Box 39)
  - WXDU Acquisition, 1992-1994 (Box 39)
  - WXDU Acquisition/Integration, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Major Speakers, circa 1993 (Box 39)
  - Major Attractions: Misc/General, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - WXDU, 1986-1993 (Box 39)
  - SALAPS [Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program], 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Budget and Finance, 1993-1994 (Box 39)
  - Budgets and Finance, 1993-1994; 1994-1995 (Box 39)
  - Media, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Development, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Interaction: General, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Union Officers, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Union Director, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Union Board: Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - University Union Board: Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Executive Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Executive Committee: General, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: Advertising, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: Brochure, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: 25th Birthday Party, October 5, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Development Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Events Council: Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Facilities: Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Finance: Meeting Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Media Council: Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Programming Council: Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Program Enhancement Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Development, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Interaction, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - The Meeting/Tom Mathabane, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Interaction, 1987-1994 (Box 47)
  - Special Events: General, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Visual Arts: General, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Media Staffing Change, 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Staff Relations 1993-1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Cynthia Pimentel, August 24-September 28, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Homecoming Band, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Quad Flix, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Sun 60, September 14, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Frank Heitman, September 20-October 22, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Widespread Panic, September 29, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Irene Roderick, September 29-November 1, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: Laughter on the 23rd Floor, October, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: Sunday in the Park, October 5-6, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Dave Matthews Band, October 8, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Bette Bates, October 24-December 3, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Vernon Pratt, November 3-December 2, 1993 (Box 47)
  - On Stage: Gus Giordano Jazz Dance, November 11, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Crystal Cawley, December 5, 1993-January 20, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Dayton Claudio, January 7-February 10, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: City of Angels, January 11-12, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: The Samples, February 13, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Anna Snowden, January 21-February 24, 1994 (Box 47)
  - On Stage: Forbidden Broadway, January 25, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Diane Rosenblum, February 11-March 14, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: From the Mississippi Delta, February 22-23, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Adam Sandler, February 25, 1994 (Box 47)
  - On Stage: The Brady Bunch, February 26, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Robert Tines, February 26-March 22, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Ani DiFranco, March 1, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Ann Trusty, March 15-April 15, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Lemonheads, March 16, 1994 (Box 47)
  - On Stage: George Winston, March 23, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Artie Dixon, March 23-May 9, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Major Attractions: Beck, March 26, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: Shirley Valentine, March 26-27, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Broadway at Duke: Shenendoah Shakespeare Express, April 7, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Special Events: Springfest - Greg Osby, April 8, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Blandine Saint-Oyant, April 17-May 23, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Shannon Bueker, May 11-June 19, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Sally Sutton, May 26-July 5, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Tony Handy, June 22-August 3, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Galleries: Katherine Schlessinger, July 8-August 17, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Visual Arts: Shows, 1993-1995 (Box 47)
  - Union Fortnight, circa 1990s (Box 47)
  - Union Weekend, October, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Fee Increase: Chronicle, 1993 (Box 47)
  - Selection, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Union Interviews (Spring), 1994 (Box 47)
  - Summer Programming, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Development Committee/Union Alumni Network, Heath L. Marcus, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Fall Retreat, 1994 (Box 47)
  - University Union Board, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Space Survey, mid-1990s (Box 47)
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Points/Flex Issue, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Union Constitutions, 1971-1994 (Box 47)
  - Finance: Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Applications [various positions], 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Program Enrichment Fund Applications, 1994 (Box 47)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1995 (Box 47)
  - Spring Retreat, 1995 (Box 47)
  - Student Organizations: Budgets, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - Finance: Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - 40th Anniversary ReUnion, April, 1995 (Box 47)
  - Minutes, 1995 (Box 47)
  - Student-Run Organizations, 1994-1995 (Box 47)
  - University Union Board, 1994-1996 (Box 47)
  - Visual Arts: Homeless, December 1, 1994-February 5, 1995 (Box 47)
  - Event Advising Center, 1994-1997 (Box 47)
  - Summer Housing, 1995 (Box 47)
  - Committee Minutes [full set], 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Union Miscellany, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - University Union Board: Meeting Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Executive Committee: Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Organizational Information, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Programming Schedule, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Union Manual, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: General, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Advertising, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Photos, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Playbill, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Brochure, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: The Secret Garden, October 11-12, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Five Guys Named Moe, October 26-27, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Second Samuel [The Alkahest Agency], November 13-14, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Oleanna, February 20, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Sisters Rosenweig, February 27-28, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: A Doll House [Acting Company], April 17-18, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Cable 13: Program Guide, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Cable 13: Chairman/Executive Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Craft Center, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Program Reports, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Development Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Events Council, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Facilities, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Finance: Year-End Finances, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Interaction, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Union Interviews, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: De La Soul, September 30, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Coffeehouse: Letters to Cleo, November 13, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: Black Moon and Jehru, December 4, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: The State, February 11, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: Dave Matthews Band, April 7, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: 311, April 7, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: Juliana Hatfield, April 15, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: Jackopierce, April 26, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Major Attractions: Etta Baker, April 29, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Media Council, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Policy Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Program Council: Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Program Enhancement Fund, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Publicity Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Quad Flix, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Retreats, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Union Strategic Plan, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Oktoberfest, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Springfest, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Visual Arts, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Slovak Art-Protis, 1994-1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Tom Buhrman, August 22-September 30, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Eugene Martin, September 13-October 24, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Jane Wells Harrison, October 3-November 27, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Kathleen A. Saccopoulos, October 26-November 28, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Frank Bianco, February 3-March 5, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Helene Dixon, March 7-31, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Jonathan Kingdom, April 3-May 15, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Ginger Gunnells, May 18-June 20, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Summer, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Retreat, Fall 1995 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Margaret McCarthy, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Galleries: Potential Shows, circa 1995 (Box 48)
  - On Stage Proposal, 1995 (Box 48)
  - WXDU: Tower/Antenna Replacement, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Homecoming, 1995 (Box 48)
  - Yearlook, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Purchase, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Special Events: Springfest, 1996 (Box 48)
  - Student Organizations: A Chosen Generation, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Bryan Center Major Donors, 1996 (Box 48)
  - Cable 13: Equipment Proposal, 1995 (Box 48)
  - End of Year Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Broadway at Duke: Sales, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - Cable 13: Alumni Lists, circa 1990s (Box 48)
  - Finance: Agendas with Notes, 1995-2000 (Box 48)
  - Finance: General, 1995-1999 (Box 48)
  - Finance: Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 48)
  - University Union Board, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Union Manual [2 folders], 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Executive Handbook, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - University Union Board: Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Budget Detail, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Committee Budgets, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Officers and Information, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Executive Committee: Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - University Union Board: Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Facilities: General, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Finance: General/Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Major Attractions, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Major Attractions: Box Office, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Shows, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Irene Stapleford, June 23-July 31, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Donna Gregory, August 23-October 7, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Major Attractions: Homecoming Concert - Step Show, October 7, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Nunsense II, October 7-8, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Ann Salisbury, October 10-November 17, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Major Attractions: Joan Osborne/Rusted Root, October 11, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Onstage: Forbidden Broadway, October 25, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Major Attractions: Gospel Fest, OCtober 29, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Jonathan Sharlin, November 20, 1995-January 2, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Crazy for You, December 6-7, 1995 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Margot McCarthy, January 17-February 23, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Angels in America, January 19-21, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Laura Lauck, January 22-March 2, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Onstage: Streb/Ringside "Popaction", February 2, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Richard Marshall, February 26-March 22, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Kiss of the Spiderwoman, March 3-5, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Greg Carter, March 4-April 8, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Shakespeare in the Garden, March 24, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Cici Stevens, March 25-April 19, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Stomp, April 1-3, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Lief-Anne Stiles, April 15-May 13, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Olivia Ollis, April 22-May 24, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: Graham M. Auman, May 30-July 8, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Quad Flix: General, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Union and GPSC, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Special Events: Tree Lighting, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Retreats and Leadership Retreat, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Semester Reports [various committees], 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Special Events, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Visual Arts: General, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Yearlook, 1996 (Box 49)
  - WXDU, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Summer Programming, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Broadway at Duke: Photos, Slides, Negatives, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Structure and History, circa 1995 (Box 49)
  - Miscellany, 1992-1995 (Box 49)
  - Union Weekend, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Summer Housing, 1996 (Box 49)
  - University Union Board: Minutes and Administrative Information, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Office Space Applications, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Office Space Applications, 1993-1995 (Box 49)
  - Chairmen Applications, 1995-1996 (Box 49)
  - Office Space Allocation, 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - WXDU: General, 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - Retreat (Spring), 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - Schedule of Events, 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - February Financial Statements, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Cable 13: Renovation Proposal, 1995 (Box 50)
  - Info Packet, 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - Clubs, 1994-1995; 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - Student-Run Organizations, 1995-1996 (Box 50)
  - Budgets, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Cable 13: University Union Board, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Cable 13: Budget Proposals, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Cable 13: General/Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Finance: Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Yearlook, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Retreat, Fall 1996 (Box 50)
  - Retreat Evaluations, Fall 1996 (Box 50)
  - Homecoming, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Interaction: Miscellaneous/General, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Retreat Info Packet, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Student Respose to West Union/Bryan Center, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Student-Run Organizations, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Performing Arts: Miscellaneous/General, 1996-1997; 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - WXDU: Miscellaneous/General, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Bryan Center Student Proposal, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Retreat, Spring 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Executive Committee: Proposals, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Annual Reports, 1996-1997; 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Semester Reports, Spring 1997 (Box 50)
  - Executive Committee: Community Liaison, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Executive Committee: Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Finance: Historical Information, 1969-1997 (Box 50)
  - Cable 13: Telly Award Information, 1996-2004 (Box 50)
  - Proposed Budgets, 1996-1997; Final Balance Sheets, 1995-1996, 1995-1997 (Box 50)
  - Fee Increase: Documents, 1997 (Box 50)
  - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - University Union Board: General, 1995-1997 (Box 50)
  - Bryan Center Information, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Media File, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Kudzu Programming, 1996-1997 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Paul Nabatoff, August 19-September 20, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Vicki Knight-Brown, November 4-December 6, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Jacqueline Hammer, December 10, 1996-January 31, 1997 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Patricia Kordas, February 2-March 10, 1997 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Amelia Papaphilippou, April 2-May 10, 1997 (Box 50)
  - GPSC, 1996-1998 (Box 50)
  - Policy, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Parliamentary Procedure, undated (Box 50)
  - Executive Event, September 23, 1997 (Box 50)
  - U Life, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Administration/Trustees, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Alumni Matters, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Alumni Network, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Endowment Fund, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Budgets and Proposals [2 folders], 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Union Manual, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Message from President Keohane, 1997-1998 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Holly Hanessian and Crystal Cawley, March 4-21, 1998 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Charles Rawlings, March 30-April 30, 1998 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: Scott Eagle, May 25-July 4, 1998 (Box 50)
  - Visual Arts: L.S. Young, July 13-August 21, 1998 (Box 50)
  - Student Surveys, Fall 1997 (Box 51)
  - Retreat, Fall 1997 (Box 51)
  - "Pole Quotes", circa 1997 (Box 51)
  - Applications [various positions], 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Finance: Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - University Union Board, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Homecoming, 1997 (Box 51)
  - Semester Reports (Fall and Spring), 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Student-Run Organizations, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Special Events: Oktoberfest, 1997 (Box 51)
  - Cable 13: Sponsorship Program, 1998 (Box 51)
  - Constitutions, 1997-1999 (Box 51)
  - Basketball Documentary: Jon Segal and Jeff Dillinger, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Policy Manual Revisions, 1997 (Box 51)
  - Financial Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Chairmen Applications, 1997-1998 (Box 51)
  - Retreat (Spring), 1998 (Box 51)